LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
UTAGE: The overwhelming desire
to make people happy.
UTAGE: When that feeling that's usually
aimed at thousands of fans
UTAGE: suddenly gets directed to one person...
SIGN: Fans Are Terrifying Creatures
TAMON: I'm sorry. I just reacted.
UTAGE: Eep...
UTAGE: After that happened, I...
UTAGE: You can't be serious.
UTAGE: Do you know how many gazillions of yen
a single karat of Tamon-kun is worth?
UTAGE: And here you are basically
giving it away for free.
SIGN: Church of Tamon
UTAGE: You're destroying the market!
SIGN: Unconditional love for Tamon Fukuhara
SIGN: Rawr
UTAGE: Please have more respect for Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: I totally lost it.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun belongs to everyone!
SIGN: Menacing
UTAGE/INT: And then I bizarrely made Tamon-kun
review the 100 Tamon Articles of Faith.
TAMON: Tamon-kun belongs to everyone...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's dreams must be
prioritized above all else!
TAMON: Tamon-kun's dreams must be
prioritized above all else.
UTAGE: Okay! Bye!
UTAGE: Please excuse me!
UTAGE/INT: I let my rage take over me
and ran right out of there.
UTAGE: Maybe I should be happy about the fact
UTAGE: that he personally showed me
full-on fan service...
SIGN: Hnnngggghhhh
UTAGE/INT: But I really think that someone who's
supposed to be a world-famous star
UTAGE/INT: shouldn't be handed out so easily!
UTAGE/INT: All of humanity needs
to respect Tamon-kun!
ALL HUMANITY: Tamon! Tamon! Tamon!
UTAGE: Why is he doing so much for me?
TAMON: I hope that Kinoshita-san will
continue coming over forever.
IMAGINARY TAMON: I love you, Kinoshita-san.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: ...Hngh!
SIGN: Thwap
SIGN: Ain't no
UTAGE: Ain't no way!
SIGN: waaaaay~
UTAGE: He's just anxious after
losing the competition for center.
UTAGE: And since he's letting all that anxiety
explode in front of me,
UTAGE: it must mean that he
has no one else he can talk to.
UTAGE: Maybe things aren't going well
with the people around him after all.
SIGN: I'll go give the Gorilla some
cannoli and bombolones!!
FUJITA: I'll go give the Gorilla
some cannoli and bombolones!
UTAGE: Fujita-san seems as busy as ever.
SIGN: Malice...
UTAGE: Their producer seems super scary.
GORILLA OURI: Go buy some butter sandwiches!
SIGN: Go buy some
butter sandwiches...
UTAGE: Ouri-kun is less a friend,
and more a rival and a gorilla.
SIGN: I'll go give the Gorilla
some cannoli and
bombolones!!
SIGN: Malice...
SIGN: Go buy some
butter sandwiches...
UTAGE: I'd like to do whatever I can
for him, but...
SIGN: Plink
SIGN: Sob Sob
SIGN: I don't think I can make it today...
I caught a cold...
SIGN: I'm sorry
UTAGE: What?!
SIGN: What?!
SIGN: Cool Sheet
UTAGE: That's rough, Yuina.
SIGN: The King of Elixirs
SIGN: Yuina
SIGN: _P Yummy, thanks
UTAGE: Oh, well. I guess I'll have to
spend the day alone.
SIGN: Goodness!
RINTARO: Goodness! I must admit,
that certainly was a close one!
RINTARO: There were more Kanpyo-chans
in places I wasn't aware of.
RINTARO: If I missed out on the rare official merch
for my oshi, Kanpyo Roll-chan,
RINTARO: I would absolutely never be
able to live with myself!
RINTARO: She showed such bravery as she quivered
in the prize machine enclosure all alone!
RINTARO: I got this close to crying at the sight,
but I gave my tear ducts a stern pep talk
RINTARO: and successfully rescued her
from her glass prison!
RINTARO: Crane games ought to be a cruel mistress,
yet I was grabbed one after another
RINTARO: as if it were an AYCE, and as a fan,
I do feel a bit conflicted about this.
RINTARO: I must be the one to let the admins know
just how in demand Kanpyo-chan is!
RINTARO: The world desires Kanpyo-chan!
RINTARO: The seven seas desire Kanpyo-chan!
RINTARO: Have I ever experienced
such a fruitful day off before?
RINTARO: Actually, I may well have.
But that doesn't matter right now.
RINTARO: I must spend every last second rescuing
Kanpyo Roll-chans from glass prisons.
SIGN: Relaxed
SIGN: Hustle
Hustle
RINTARO: That is my sworn duty for today!
SIGN: Pull
RINTARO: Onward ho! Until my time
of leisure comes to an end!
SIGN: Pull
RINTARO: Knowing that all of the other Kanpyo fans
are also acting with happiness
RINTARO: and gratitude in their hearts
naturally gives...
UTAGE: I get you... The love
that we have for our oshis.
SIGN: Kappa Rolls
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san?!
UTAGE: What are you doing here?
SIGN: Huff...
TAMON: Kinoshita-san...
TAMON: I'm so happy to run into you
in a place like this...
SIGN: Huff...
TAMON: Kinoshita-san...
SIGN: Inch...
UTAGE: H-Hello...
TAMON: Do you have the day off today?
SIGN: Inch...
UTAGE: Er, yes...
TAMON: Because... You think I'm hot.
TAMON: If I get too close, he'll start giving out
Hottiehara-kun for free again.
SIGN: Wobble
Wobble
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, please wait...
UTAGE: I'm in a hurry!
TAMON: Kinoshita-san!
SIGN: Vrooooooom
UTAGE: Huh?!
UTAGE: His paper bag turned all fancy
and he suddenly got faster!
UTAGE: He caught up...?!
SIGN: Konk
SIGN: Craaash
SIGN: Drench
TAMON: I-It's so hot...
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: It's a sauna under here
SIGN: Huff...
UTAGE: How could you run around
in midsummer heat wearing that?
UTAGE: What're you going to do
if Tamon-kun gets heatstroke?!
TAMON: I'm sorry. I'll be more careful.
UTAGE: Do you have the day off as well,
Gloomyhara-san?
TAMON: I have some downtime
from work right now...
TAMON: I'm sorry that someone like me
was having fun.
UTAGE: Oh, no. I'm actually glad that
you have some hobbies.
TAMON: Sometimes there're kappa
wrapped in really unique ways...
SIGN: Roll...
TAMON: They're rare ones.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Rare
SIGN: Super Rare
UTAGE: Those are the figures that're
at his place, aren't they?
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's using the money we offer him
to buy himself Kappa Rolls for self-care.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Rare
SIGN: Super Rare
SIGN: Moved...
UTAGE: That makes me happy.
TAMON: I just wanted to give you one
because I got a dupe...
TAMON: Why did you run away like that?
UTAGE: You're actually about 100 cm taller
than we think you are.
UTAGE: So having you run at me when you're
that big is extremely intimidating.
SIGN: Image 80 cm
UTAGE: Wait, I shouldn't be talking to him!
UTAGE: I shouldn't be interacting
with my oshi outside of work!
SIGN: This is a
crazy otaku
SIGN: I'm sorry for
SIGN: what I did
UTAGE: I'll be paraded around town,
guilty of crazy fan crimes.
CROWD: It's a crazy fan!
CROWD: She's guilty!
CROWD: Well, I'll be going now!
CROWD: Make sure you properly recharge
and good luck at work!
SIGN: Step
TAMON: Ah!
TAMON: Um... would you like
to have lunch toge...
UTAGE: Absolutely not.
SIGN: Ruthless
TAMON: I guess you really do
just see me as trash...
TAMON: I got too cocky. I guess I'll die now.
UTAGE: Please stop!
UTAGE: Only love, acclaim, and cheers are allowed
to be pointed at Tamon-kun!
SIGN: Limp
UTAGE: Not this!
SIGN: Eek
UTAGE: Today's my oshi activities day!
UTAGE: I'm making my pilgrimage
UTAGE: and going to places you've
already been to, Tamon-kun.
TAMON: That sounds even better.
TAMON: I'll give you a tour!
UTAGE: Bang!
SIGN: Boom
UTAGE: He doesn't get it at all...
TAMON: This is...
TAMON: The place we had a location
shoot at the other day.
UTAGE: Yes. It's a very popular shop
right now thanks to you.
UTAGE: One bite of a sandwich here helps you feel
that Tamon-kun is real and in this world.
UTAGE: When these two worlds that would usually
never intertwine hit your tastebuds,
SIGN: Swoon
UTAGE: what fills your mouth is never-ending love
and just a little bit of guilt.
TAMON: O-Oh, I see...
TAMON: And what are they doing over there?
RANDO GIRL 1: I feel the aura he left behind.
RANDO GIRL 2: You can feel the negative ions.
UTAGE: They are respecting
the ground Tamon-kun stood on.
RANDO GIRL 3: It's just so cool.
TAMON: The ground...
UTAGE: Every single spot our oshi has been
becomes a power spot.
TAMON: I don't really get it,
TAMON: but if it makes everyone that happy,
TAMON: maybe I'll crawl around on all fours
at the next location shoot.
RIGHT UTAGE: I love you.
LEFT UTAGE: But please don't.
SIGN: Ta-daaah!
BOTH: Let's eat.
UTAGE: Okay.
SIGN: Click
TAMON: Is it fun taking photos of me
with the sandwiches?
SIGN: Click
UTAGE: It's the funnest thing in the world.
TAMON: Would this make it even more fun?
TAMON: You can take as many as you'd like.
SIGN: Tamon-kun
UTAGE: So many Tamon-kuns?!
SIGN: They're all Tamon-kun?!
UTAGE: So hot! I'm fizzling out!
SIGN: Fizzling Out
TAMON: Huh?
TAMON: Kinoshita-san?!
Kinoshita-san?! Where'd you go?
UTAGE: If someone who wants
to express themselves is an artist
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Utage's remains
UTAGE: and someone who wants
to entertain others is an entertainer,
UTAGE: it goes without saying
which group Tamon-kun belongs to.
SIGN: Japanese Instruments
UTAGE: The F/ACE section's gotten even bigger!
The world is catching up to F/ACE!
UTAGE: Congratulations, world!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is so hot!
TAMON: Huh...
UTAGE: And yet, this is...
SIGN: Boom
TAMON: Hey, that's cute.
UTAGE: This...
UTAGE: cannot be allowed!
SIGN: Staaaare
TAMON: Hey, are you having fun?
UTAGE: Er, y-yes.
SIGN: Boom
UTAGE: How can I make him understand?!
UTAGE: That Hottiehara-kun mustn't be handed out
just to sate one girl's personal desires!
UTAGE: Oh, I know!
SIGN: Gasp
UTAGE: I have an extra ticket
since Yuina wasn't able to come along.
SIGN: Center Competition Documentary
SIGN: Yuina
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san! Let's go see a movie!
TAMON: Huh?!
TAMON: If you don't mind me
coming along, of course.
SIGN: Oooooooh
SIGN: Center Competition Documentary
SIGN: Siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiigh
NARRATOR: They were given the name "F/ACE" so they
could become the face of a generation.
UTAGE: I've seen this movie ten times
and cried ten times,
UTAGE: but it might be torture
for Tamon-kun to watch it...
NARRATOR: Our coverage covers
the announcement of their new song...
UTAGE: But even then, I want him to know...
SHIRAISHI: This competition to choose the center
SHIRAISHI: is a challenge that'll
take F/ACE to new heights.
UTAGE: That I like the Tamon-kun who tries hard
for everyone. Not just for me.
TAMON: Bring it on.
TAMON: Acting cool isn't
the only part of our job.
TAMON: Come at me with everything you've got.
UTAGE: That he's that cool.
SHIRAISHI: The title of the new song is "RAIN."
SHIRAISHI: It takes the regrets a man feels when
he realizes the weight of what he's lost
SHIRAISHI: and turns it into a lyrical melody...
a ballad about heartbreak.
SHIRAISHI: And for the first episode...
TAMON: I was honestly surprised
that we were repicking the center.
TAMON: But F/ACE is a group
that's forever evolving,
TAMON: so this is just a hurdle
that I need to get over.
TAMON: Great job.
SONG: RAIN starts falling
SONG: Washing everything away
SONG: Why couldn't I realize it back then?
SONG: The sky in a morning without you—
so carelessly clear
SONG: The RAIN won't stop
UTAGE: Even if you're suffering,
please don't ever forget...
SONG: Under the sky, I start running
UTAGE: That your dream
is right there, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: I want you to see that.
UTAGE: Gah! That was
the absolute best of the best!
SIGN: Waaaaaaaaah!!
UTAGE: Were you watching carefully,
Gloomyhara-san?
UTAGE: Now do you understand
how valuable Tamon-kun is?
TAMON: Er, no...
TAMON: I honestly barely looked at the screen.
TAMON: It was too much torture.
UTAGE: What?!
UTAGE: It's no use...
TAMON: But...
TAMON: It looked like you
were having a lot of fun...
TAMON: and you seemed really happy.
TAMON: You weren't making those expressions
before seeing the movie.
UTAGE: Well, that's because... um...
UTAGE: It's just because
I love Tamon-kun so much.
TAMON: I'd love to see that again.
TAMON: If I make my dream come true,
TAMON: would that make you as happy
as you are right now again?
UTAGE: I'd be the happiest girl in the world!
UTAGE: Maybe he does understand a little bit...
TAMON: Oh, yeah. I forgot about this.
TAMON: You can have this.
UTAGE: Oh, thank you very much...
SIGN: Dash
UTAGE: What?! Wait, isn't this the rare one?
Gloomyhara-san!
NARRATOR: Decorate your bathroom with Kappa Rolls.
PHOTOGRAPHER: You're in top form today, Tamon-kun.
STAFF A: He's exploding with sexiness.
STAFF B: I can feel my collagen
replenishing itself just watching him.
FUJITA: I thought he'd be dwelling about the fact
that he lost the center position more,
FUJITA: but he got right back onto his feet.
FUJITA: He's not even scared to work. Actually...
FUJITA: This is your next job.
FUJITA/INT: Here comes another nervous breakdown.
TAMON: Okay, I'll do it.
FUJITA: You'll be fine! You don't need
to be so scared...
FUJITA: Wait, what?
TAMON: Thank you for everything
you do, Fujita-san.
FUJITA: I need to thank Kinoshita-san.
FUJITA: Because of her,
I've got one less bald spot.
UTAGE: Huh? He's not answering?
UTAGE: Huh?!
KEITO: Good evening.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
KEITO: You're Kinoshita-san... right?
KEITO: You're Tamon's housekeeper.
UTAGE: I was just trying to go
to Tamon-kun's place as usual,
UTAGE: and then Keito-kun greeted me
for some reason.
UTAGE: I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
SIGN: Tamon-kun
SIGN: National Treasure
SIGN: So hot
IMAGINARY KEITO: Tamon-kun is a national treasure!
UTAGE: Keito Tachibana-kun.
UTAGE: Trusted by the Church of Tamon followers,
UTAGE: he loves his group mates and has
the friendliest, most relatable persona!
UTAGE: What is F/ACE's leader
and current center doing here?!
UTAGE: I mean, he probably lives here,
but what's he doing in front of me?!
KEITO: Want to come over to my place right now?
KEITO: Er, I don't mean anything weird by that.
KEITO: Tamon and Ouri are also over right now.
You know them, right?
KEITO: Will you let me thank you for
taking care of the others all the time?
UTAGE: I wouldn't say I've done that much...
UTAGE: It's not like I could just go
into Tamon-kun's place so...
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Tamon-kun's
Apartment
KEITO: Here we are. I'd like to thank you,
but I can really only offer you tea.
UTAGE: Um...
UTAGE: You live next door to Tamon-kun.
I never even realized...
KEITO: Well, we do usually go home
at separate times.
KEITO: Come in.
UTAGE: Oh, thank you...
UTAGE: It's dark. It's immediately dark.
SIGN: Poverty
UTAGE: Wow, the layout of his place
is exactly the same as next door.
MUSHROOM: Gloomy, gloom.
MUSHROOM: I can tell which belong
to whom in a single glance.
SIGN: Time Is\hMoney
SIGN: A Yen Saved Is a Yen Earned
KEITO: Okay, everyone have a seat.
SIGN: Work Hard and
Practice Frugality
UTAGE: Huh?
OURI: What the hell are you doing here?
I bet you came to see me—
UTAGE: Absolutely not.
TAMON: I'm sorry I couldn't answer the door.
KEITO: I called everyone over.
KEITO: First, could you take a look at this?
KEITO: Do you mind explaining this?
UTAGE: This is from yesterday?! When did he...
KEITO: The last time I spotted you two,
KEITO: it was at our apartment building,
so I let it slide...
KEITO: But are you really just a housekeeper?
OURI: You guys met outside again?
Who do you think you are?!
KEITO: Wait. What do you mean, "again"?
UTAGE: W-We just happened to run into each other!
TAMON: It really was a coincidence.
Though I had fun.
UTAGE: Wha—
OURI: Well, I invited her over
to my parents' place twice.
UTAGE: Hey.
KEITO: Seriously?
SIGN: Work Hard and
Practice Frugality
KEITO: She's got you both wrapped
around her finger. How pathetic.
KEITO: I guess things are worse
than I suspected.
KEITO: Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: Yes?
KEITO: We're trying to become world famous.
KEITO: Our first album was a hit
KEITO: and our Dome performance being
a success put us in the mainstream.
KEITO: Our appearances on TV have
also been growing steadily.
KEITO: This is our moment of truth.
KEITO: I'm absolutely going to make F/ACE
a group that represents this generation!
UTAGE: Keito-kun...
UTAGE: He really is a leader that cares
for his group like we thought.
KEITO: We're gonna swindle
the fans out of all their money,
KEITO: and I'm gonna go down
in history as a millionaire.
SIGN: Shock!
SIGN: Ke
SIGN: Keke
SIGN: Kekeke...
KEITO: As you know, these two are
the dual poster boys for F/ACE.
SIGN: Frugality Is a Virtue
KEITO: These two can make or break our group.
SIGN: Flash
KEITO: Stop deceiving our precious
golden geese, you wicked fangirl!
KEITO: Wicked fangirl! Wicked fangirl!
SIGN: Golden
UTAGE: Golden... geese?
SIGN: Golden...
Geese
UTAGE: Really? This is what he's like?
KEITO: Fans like you need to stop meddling
and just quietly act as our sustenance.
KEITO: A fan that doesn't know
their place is worthless.
OURI: I'm not gonna let that slide,
you old scrooge!
KEITO: Who're you calling old? I'm only twenty.
TAMON: Excuse me...
TAMON: Could you not...
TAMON: speak to my fan like that?
TAMON: I know there are certain people
that you dislike, Keito-kun...
TAMON: But you really shouldn't
say things like that.
OURI: I actually agree with him for once.
OURI: I always thought that was rather
shitty of you, you shithead!
KEITO: What?!
OURI: Don't act all surprised!
I never say the same thing twice.
KEITO: You literally just said "shit" twice.
UTAGE: So I guess things weren't going well
with the other members after all...
OURI: I only said the truth.
UTAGE: Actually, they're not
getting along at all.
SIGN: Shake
SIGN: Quiver
KEITO: Is that seriously the extent
of your vocabulary?
UTAGE: There's no way Tamon-kun can be
mentally stable in this situation.
TAMON: You guys, violence is ba...
OURI: Shut up!
KEITO: You stay out of this.
TAMON: I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry that
my whole existence is a burden.
UTAGE: But it's not like an outsider like me
can butt into their problems...
UTAGE: Not to mention...
KEITO: Fans are terrifying creatures.
KEITO: They're ruthless beasts who engage
in bloody quarrels with each other.
SIGN: Waaaaaaaaah
SIGN: Rumble
KEITO: They rival the CIA in gathering intel...
CRAZY FAN: Keito-kun!
SIGN: Stick...
KEITO: and tailing others.
KEITO: They're insane!
SIGN: Tremble
UTAGE: Wait, I have heard that a certain part of
Keito-kun's fandom is off their rockers.
OURI: Are there actually fans like that?
SIGN: Shake Shake
KEITO: There are!
SIGN: Point
KEITO: As a prime example, this woman has
clearly infiltrated your private lives!
SIGN: Point
KEITO: She's an evil fan who will
lead you both to your demise!
KEITO: As proof, you both failed
in the competition for center!
KEITO: You two should've been able to...
TAMON: Keito-kun?
KEITO: If you mean well at all,
never come near these two again.
OURI: Hey! You don't have the right
to enforce anything like that!
KEITO: This is an order as the leader.
UTAGE: It's true that Tamon-kun
wasn't able to become the center.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun realizes that...
more than anyone else.
UTAGE: It's true that I'm a Tamon-kun fan.
UTAGE: I can't blame anyone
for thinking that about me.
SIGN: Under One Sky, We
Strive for the Same Goal
UTAGE: Thinking logically, he's 100% right.
I should back away.
UTAGE: But...
TAMON: If I make my dream come true,
TAMON: would that make you as happy
as you are right now again?
UTAGE: Even then...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's worries,
his smile, his hard work...
UTAGE: I can't imagine they're for nothing.
UTAGE: It's true that I'm a fan.
UTAGE: And I'm always conflicted about whether
UTAGE: it's actually bad for me to be around him.
UTAGE: But...
SIGN: Blackfin Sea Bass
SIGN: Stingy and Frugal Are
Not the Same
SIGN: Constant Dripping
Wears Away
the Stone
UTAGE: Whenever I'm around Gloomyhara-san,
it's solely as his housekeeper.
UTAGE: And as his housekeeper,
I've done everything I can for him.
UTAGE: Ugh, what am I even doing?
UTAGE: I had just decided that I'd keep
my distance from Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Maybe I am just a crazy fan after all.
UTAGE: Um... And your manager is
the one who officially hired me, so...
KEITO: Our manager authorized this?
What the hell is Fujita-san thinking?
FUJITA: Kinoshita-san!
UTAGE: Fujita-san?!
FUJITA: Oh, there you are. Thank goodness.
FUJITA: Hm? What are you all doing here?
UTAGE: How did you know I was here?
FUJITA: I found this in front
of Keito's apartment.
SIGN: Tamon-kun
OURI: How do you keep dropping that thing?
FUJITA: I actually have a request
for you, Kinoshita-san.
FUJITA: Will you participate in
F/ACE's training camp?!
SIGN: B
o
m
SIGN: B
o
m
ALL: What?!
SIGN: What?!
UTAGE: Training camp?
FUJITA: It's going to be for a show.
FUJITA: To hit the ground running
as the new F/ACE,
FUJITA: we're going to have them
strengthen their bonds.
UTAGE: I wanna watch that.
FUJITA: We call it "F/ACE's Super Exciting
Summer Trip (TBD)".
OURI: Talk about lame.
KEITO: Stop picking your ears
in my damn apartment.
KEITO: Hey!
KEITO: Wait a minute.
I have a ton of questions...
KEITO: But let's start with what's going on here.
FUJITA: The part-timer we hired to help
with the show won't be able to make it.
FUJITA: And as you know, the real F/ACE is a mess.
OURI: Don't call us a mess!
FUJITA: And we don't want others
finding out about our mess!
SIGN: Grawr
KEITO: So rather than hiring someone
who you don't know temporarily,
KEITO: it's safer to bring this woman along
because she's in the know already?
FUJITA: Exactly.
UTAGE: But this is too sudden!
UTAGE: I have no idea how to do
talent agency work.
FUJITA: Don't worry, you'll be fine.
FUJITA: I'll make sure to contact your parents
and it'll just be supplementary work,
FUJITA: so we can't pay much,
but we'll definitely pay you.
FUJITA: It's summer break, right?
Sign: Blackfin Sea Bass
FUJITA: You have time, don't you?
Sign: Time Is Money
FUJITA: You want money, don't you?!
UTAGE: W-Well, yes, but...
TAMON: This is bothering Kinoshita-san...
FUJITA: Tamon.
FUJITA: If we hire someone new, you won't be
able to let your guard down for a second.
Sign: Today's Savings Is
Tomorrow's Happiness
FUJITA: Are you okay with that?
KEITO: I guess we don't have a choice, then.
KEITO: Tamon's true personalty hasn't been
revealed to the rest of the world.
KEITO: That must mean
you've kept your mouth shut.
KEITO: I guess I can trust you there.
KEITO: I'm also against doing anything risky...
UTAGE: Wait a minute...
KEITO: But fans are still rotten anyway.
KEITO: I'll reveal who you really are during
the two-night, three-day camp.
UTAGE: I can't keep up with all of this.
Are you serious?
OURI: She'll do fine. Let's take her.
UTAGE: Don't decide for m—
TAMON: I'd also have you come along
rather than someone we don't know...
ALL: Ooh!
Sign: Ooooooh
FUJITA: That's that.
OURI: Hell yeah!
TAMON: We'll be in your care.
UTAGE: What?!
FUJITA: I'll fill you in on the details later.
FUJITA: We'll be leaving in three days,
so please be ready by then!
Sign: Dash!!
UTAGE: Fujita-san!
KEITO: Don't go selling private photos of us.
Sign: Glare...
UTAGE: I will not!
OURI: I'll bring you around
by the time the trip is over!
Sign: Super Excited
UTAGE: Around to what?!
TAMON: A multi-day trip. I'm gonna throw up.
Sign: Wanna Throw Up...
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is a god!
UTAGE: This is a mess!
UTAGE: I guess summer's nowhere near over yet.
Credits: \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Credits: Michelle Tymon
\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
Credits: \h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Credits: Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom